mitsubishicars.com 2016-05-04

# Privacy | Mitsubishi Motors

### Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc. 

Thank you for visiting the official website of Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc (MMNA). This privacy policy explains how personal information about you is collected, used and disclosed by MMNA with respect to your use of the MMNA websites where this policy is posted (collectively, "Sites").

### Information Collected by MMNA

_General_

Our Sites are made available to you to provide information about our products and services. You can browse our Sites without providing any personal information such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number or social security number.

 _Non-Personal Information_

When you access and use our Sites, some information is automatically collected. For example, we may collect information about your computer's operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type and language, and the website that referred you to us. We also collect information about your usage and activity on our Sites.

**Cookies.**  
When you visit our Sites, you may be issued a "cookie," which helps track your session while online. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive. Among other things, cookies help to make your site visit more relevant and personalized for you. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Sites. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you may set your browser to refuse cookies or alert you when cookies are being sent; however, it is possible that some parts of our Sites will not function properly if you do so.

**Web Beacons.**  
The Sites and any communications sent by MMNA may contain electronic images (generally, single pixel ".gif" images) called "web beacons." These web beacons allow MMNA and third parties to monitor and collect certain information about the viewer of a web page, email message or other communication, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, the device identifier of the device the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed. Web beacons may be used count unique users, visits and page views; monitor traffic and conversion patterns; personalize your experience when you visit the Sites, including advertising and content you see; and determine whether or not messages were opened, links were clicked and/or notifications/offers were acted upon.

**Third Party Advertising.**  
We may also allow third parties to use cookies or other tracking technologies to collect non-personal information about your use of our Sites, including your IP address, pages viewed and conversion information. This information may be used, among other things, to deliver advertising targeted to your interests and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Sites and other sites tracked by these third parties. This privacy policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third party cookies or other tracking technologies. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn more about their privacy practices. If you would like more information about third party advertising or to opt out of having your information used in this way, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

 _Personal Information_

We also collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as when you register for an account, participate in a promotion or sweepstakes, request a brochure or other materials, sign up to test drive a vehicle, locate or make inquiries to a Mitsubishi Dealer, request a credit score estimate or otherwise contact MMNA. Such information may include: contact information (name, address, telephone number, social media username/handle, mobile phone, and/or email address); vehicle information (make, model, year, condition, purchase and service dealerships, dates of ownership or lease, and vehicle identification numbers); financial information (credit application history, missed payment history, current and estimated loan payments, etc.); demographic information (age, marital status, size of household, income); and marketing profile information (when you plan to purchase or lease a vehicle, the Mitsubishi vehicle you are interested in, etc.). We may also collect the names and email addresses of your friends and family, if you choose to provide MMNA with this information. Finally, we may obtain information from other sources and combine that with the information we collect directly from you. 

### How We Use Your Information

_Non-Personal Information_

Non-personal information is used to generate statistics and to measure site activity in order to improve the usefulness of the site for our visitors.

 _Personal Information_

Personal information allows us to provide you with products, services and information and enables us to offer a customized experience on our Sites. We use personal information for the purposes described in this privacy policy or otherwise disclosed to you on our Sites. For example, personal information may be used to: 

  * operate and improve our Sites
  * provide information about our products and send you related information, including confirmations, brochures, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * notify you of the closest Mitsubishi dealer;
  * process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
  * respond to comments, questions, or requests for information and provide customer service;
  * communicate with you about our vehicles, new contests, promotions, rewards, special offers, upcoming events and other news about MMNA and our selected partners;
  * generate site analytics to improve our website and the user experience; and
  * link or combine with personal information we get from third parties to help understand your needs and provide you with better service.

MMNA may store and process personal information in the United States and other countries. 

### Sharing Your Information

We do not share your personal information with third parties except as described in this privacy policy or as otherwise disclosed to you on our Sites. For example, we may share personal information as follows:

  * with our wholly owned subsidiary, Mitsubishi Motors Credit of America, Inc (MMCA) for the purpose of offering products and services to our customers;
  * with authorized Mitsubishi dealers to honor your request for a price quote on a vehicle or trade-in appraisal, or to provide a dealer with information in order to contact you in its regular course of business, including for marketing purposes;
  * with authorized Mitsubishi dealers when you use the credit score estimator for purposes of facilitating the car buying process and, if applicable, verifying the trade-in value of your vehicle;
  * with certain unaffiliated third parties to provide select products and services to you (including but not limited to car insurance, safe and uninterrupted electric service for i-MiEV drivers, etc.);
  * when you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you on the Sites that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information;
  * with vendors, contractors, consultants and other service providers who are working on our behalf and need access to your information to carry out their work for us;
  * to (i) comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process, (ii) to protect our rights and property and those of our agents, customers and others, including to enforce our agreements, policies and Terms of Use or (iii) in an emergency to protect MMNA and the safety of our customers, employees or any third party; and
  * in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, restructuring, reorganization, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

We may also share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you. 

### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California's Shine the Light law, Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83, California residents have the right to request and obtain, once per year, information regarding MMNA's disclosure of personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. To request a list of the categories of information MMNA has shared, and the names and addresses of such third parties, please send your request to:

Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc.  
Customer Relations Department  
PO Box 6400  
Cypress, CA 90630

### Updating Your Information

If you provided MMNA with personal information, you may review and update that information by logging into your online account.

### Opt Out Option and Correcting Your Information

You may opt out of receiving promotional emails and SMS messages from MMNA at any time by visiting http://www.mitsubishicars.com/preferences and changing your communication preferences. To opt out of SMS messages, you can also text MITSUSTOP from the cell phone that you have registered with MMNA. In addition, you can opt out of receiving promotional emails by following the instructions in those emails, but note that we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your account or our ongoing business relations. You may also request changes to your contact preferences and the personal information by writing to:

Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc.   
Customer Relations Department  
PO Box 6400  
Cypress, CA 90630

### Information Security

We take reasonable measures to protect personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

### Third Party Links

Our Sites may contain links to third party websites. This privacy policy does not apply to the linked sites, and we do not control, nor are we responsible for, the content or privacy and security practices of those sites. Any personal information you provide to a linked site is provided directly to a third party and is subject to such third party's privacy policy. We encourage you to learn more about such third party's privacy and security practices and policies before providing any of your personal information.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact MMNA by calling 1-888-MITSU (1-888-648-7820).

### Privacy Policy Effective Date

MMNA may change this privacy policy from time to time. If MMNA makes any changes to this policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date below.

Last Updated: October 15th, 2013

### Electronic Records Disclosure

Last Update: October 16th, 2013

**Please read this Electronic Records Disclosure carefully. This disclosure informs you of your rights when we provide certain disclosures, notices, and other information ("Records") to you electronically through the mitsubishicars.com website and via email.**

The words, "I," "you" and "your," mean the user requesting information from this website. The words, "MMCA," "we," "us" and "our," mean Mitsubishi Motors Credit of America, Inc. and its agents and affiliates, including Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc.

**(1) Introduction**  
Certain laws require us to provide specific Records to you in writing, which means you have a right to receive those Records on paper. We may provide such Records to you electronically if we first present this Electronic Records Disclosure to you and you consent to the use of electronic Records. By indicating your agreement to this Electronic Records Disclosure, you agree that your electronic signature on agreements and documents has the same effect as if you signed them in ink.

**(2) Types of Electronic Records You May Receive**  
By consenting to the use of electronic Records, you acknowledge receipt of this Electronic Records Disclosure and you consent to receive Records electronically. Records may be presented on the mitsubishicars.com website and via e-mail at the email address you provide (assuming you provide a valid e-mail address). Electronic Records may include, but are not limited to: 

  * This Electronic Records Disclosure; and
  * Consent to be contacted by telephone; and
  * An offer of credit, if eligible.

**(3) How to Withdraw Your Consent**  
Your consent to the use of electronic Records will remain in force until withdrawn in the manner provided in this section. If you withdraw your consent, we will stop providing you with electronic Records. Your withdrawal of consent will apply only to the request for services you are now seeking. You may withdraw your consent free of charge by emailing us at info@yourmitsu.com. Be sure to specify your name and the address to which we should mail future Records as necessary. Your withdrawal of consent will be effective only after MMCA has had a reasonable period to act upon your withdrawal request.

**(4) Updating Your Contact Information**  
If your e-mail address or other contact information changes, you must notify MMCA of such change immediately by emailing us at info@yourmitsu.com.

**(5) Obtaining Paper Copies of Electronic Records**  
You may print or make a copy of electronic Records by using the "Print" button or using your personal computer's printing function. Upon request, we will provide you with a paper copy of any Record. We must receive your request within 60 days after the date we first made the electronic Record available to you. You may request a paper copy of any Record by emailing us at info@yourmitsu.com. Be sure to specify your name, the specific Record for which you are requesting a paper copy, and the address to which we should mail it. We will not charge you for a paper copy of the Record.

**(6) Hardware and Software Requirements**  
While you may be able to access and retain electronic Records using other hardware and software, your personal computer needs to support the following:

An operating system, such as:

  * Windows NT, 2000, ME, XP, Vista, or Win 7; or
  * Macintosh OS 10.x

Access to the Internet and an Internet browser that supports standard HTML and JavaScript, such as the browser you are now using to view this Electronic Records Disclosure, or:

  * Microsoft Internet Explorer 8.0 or higher
  * Firefox 17.0 or higher
  * Safari 5.0 or higher

We will provide electronic Records on the mitsubishicars.com website and via email in either HTML and/or PDF format. For electronic Records provided in PDF format, Adobe Reader® is required. You may download a free copy of Adobe Reader® from the Adobe website at[ www.adobe.com.](http://www.adobe.com/) Link opens new window. You are responsible for providing us with a valid e-mail address.

To print or download electronic Records you must have a printer connected to your computer or up to approximately 1 MB of available hard drive space to store electronic Records.

**(7) Retain Copies for Your Records**  
We recommend you print or download a copy of this Electronic Records Disclosure and all other electronic Records to retain for your personal records.

### Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc.

Gracias por visitar el sitio web oficial de Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc (MMNA). Esta política de privacidad explica cómo la información personal sobre usted, es recopilada usada y divulgada por MMNA con respecto a su uso de los sitios web de MMNA donde esta política está publicada (colectivamente, los "Sitios").

### Información Recopilada por MMNA

_General_

Nuestros Sitios se ponen a su disposición para proporcionarle información sobre nuestros productos y servicios. Usted puede navegar por nuestros sitios sin proporcionar ninguna información personal como su nombre, dirección postal, dirección de correo electrónico, número de teléfono o número de seguro social.

Información No Personal  
Cuando usted accede y utiliza nuestros Sitios, cierta información es recogida de forma automática. Por ejemplo, podremos recopilar información sobre el sistema operativo de su ordenador, su dirección IP, sus horarios de acceso, su tipo de navegador e idioma y el sitio web que lo refirió a nosotros. También recogemos información sobre su uso de nuestros Sitios y la actividad que realiza en los mismos.

**Cookies.**  
Cuando usted visita nuestros Sitios, es posible que le sea entregado un "cookie", que ayuda a monitorear su sesión mientras esté en línea. Los cookies son pequeños archivos de datos almacenados en su unidad de disco duro. Entre otras cosas, los cookies ayudan a que su visita al lugar sea más relevante y personalizada. Utilizamos cookies para ver qué áreas y funciones son populares y para contar las visitas a nuestros Sitios. La mayoría de los navegadores web están configurados de forma predeterminada para aceptar cookies. Si usted lo prefiere, puede configurar su navegador para rechazar los cookies o para que le avise cuando se le envíen cookies. Sin embargo, es posible que algunas partes de nuestros sitios no funcionen correctamente si usted lo hace.

**Balizas Web.**  
Los Sitios y cualquier comunicación enviada por MMNA pueden contener imágenes electrónicas (generalmente, imágenes de un solo píxel de tipo ".gif") llamadas "balizas web". Estas balizas web permiten que MMNA y terceros monitoreen y recopilen cierta información sobre el visitante de una página web, mensaje de correo electrónico u otras comunicaciones, tales como el tipo de navegador que solicita la baliza web, el identificador de dispositivo del dispositivo al cual se está enviando la baliza web y el momento en que la baliza web fue visualizada. Las balizas web pueden ser utilizadas para contar usuarios únicos, visitas y visualizaciones de páginas, monitorear los patrones de tráfico y conversión, personalizar su experiencia cuando usted visita los Sitios, incluyendo la publicidad y el contenido que usted ve y determinar si se abrieron o no mensajes, se hizo clic sobre enlaces y/o si se actuó en función de notificaciones/ofertas.

**Publicidad de Terceros.**  
También podremos permitir que terceros utilicen cookies u otras tecnologías de seguimiento para recopilar información no personal sobre el uso de nuestros Sitios, incluyendo su dirección IP, las páginas visitadas y la información de conversión. Esta información podrá ser utilizada, entre otras cosas, para entregar publicidad que a usted le pudiera interesar y para comprender mejor el uso y las visitas a nuestros Sitios y otros sitios monitoreados por dichos terceros. Esta política de privacidad no se aplica a cookies u otras tecnologías de seguimiento de terceros. Le sugerimos que revise las políticas de privacidad de los anunciantes y/o servicios de anuncios para obtener más información acerca de sus prácticas de privacidad. Si usted desea obtener más información acerca de la publicidad de terceros o desea ejercer su opción de no permitir que su información sea utilizada de esta manera (opt out), por favor visite <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Información Personal**  
También recopilamos la información personal que usted nos proporcione voluntariamente, por ejemplo, cuando usted se registre para una cuenta, participe en una promoción o sorteo, solicite un folleto u otros materiales, se inscriba para una prueba de conducción de un vehículo, localice o realice consultas a un concesionario Mitsubishi, solicite una estimación de calificación crediticia o se contacte de alguna otra manera con MMNA. Dicha información podrá incluir: información de contacto (nombre, dirección, número de teléfono, nombre de usuario en medios sociales, teléfono móvil y/o dirección de correo electrónico), información de vehículo (marca, modelo, año, estado, concesionarios de compra y de servicio, fechas de propiedad o arrendamiento y números de identificación del vehículo), información financiera (historial de solicitudes de crédito, historial de pagos no cumplidos, pagos de préstamos actuales y estimados, etc.), información demográfica (edad, estado civil, cantidad de integrantes del hogar, ingresos) e información sobre su perfil de marketing (cuándo piensa proceder a la compra o el arrendamiento de un vehículo, el vehículo Mitsubishi que le interesa, etc.). También podremos recopilar los nombres y direcciones de correo electrónico de sus amigos y familiares, si usted proporciona esta información a MMNA. Por último, podremos obtener información de otras fuentes y combinarla con la información que obtenemos directamente de usted.

### Cómo Utilizamos su Información

_Información No Personal_

La información no personal es utilizada para generar estadísticas y medir la actividad del sitio a fin de mejorar la utilidad del sitio para nuestros visitantes.

 _Información Personal_

La información personal nos permite proporcionarle productos, servicios e información y nos permite ofrecerle una experiencia personalizada en nuestros Sitios. Utilizamos la información personal para los fines descritos en esta política de privacidad o revelados de otra manera en nuestros sitios. Por ejemplo, la información personal podrá ser utilizada para:

  * operar y mejorar nuestros Sitios
  * proporcionar información sobre nuestros productos y enviarle información relacionada, incluyendo confirmaciones, folletos, avisos técnicos, actualizaciones, alertas de seguridad y mensajes de soporte y administrativos;
  * comunicarle a usted sobre el concesionario Mitsubishi más cercano;
  * procesar participaciones en concursos y entregar premios;
  * responder a los comentarios, preguntas o solicitudes de información y proporcionar servicio al cliente;
  * comunicarnos con usted acerca de nuestros vehículos, nuevos concursos, promociones, premios, ofertas especiales, próximos eventos y otras noticias sobre MMNA y nuestros socios selectos;
  * generar análisis de sitio para mejorar nuestro sitio web y la experiencia del usuario; y
  * vincularla o combinarla con la información personal que obtengamos de terceros para ayudar a entender sus necesidades y ofrecerle un mejor servicio.

MMNA podrá almacenar y procesar información personal dentro de los Estados Unidos y en otros países. 

### Compartir su Información

No compartimos su información personal con terceros, excepto según se describe en esta política de privacidad o según lo revelado en nuestros Sitios. Por ejemplo, podremos compartir la información personal de la siguiente manera:

  * con la filial que nos pertenece totalmente, Mitsubishi Motors Credit of America, Inc (MMCA) con el propósito de ofrecer productos y servicios a nuestros clientes;
  * con los concesionarios autorizados de Mitsubishi para cumplir con su solicitud de una cotización de precio para un vehículo o una tasación para una permuta, o para proporcionar a un concesionario la información necesaria para ponerse en contacto con usted en el curso normal de los negocios, incluso para fies de marketing;
  * con los concesionarios autorizados de Mitsubishi cuando usted utiliza un estimador de calificación crediticia a los efectos de facilitar el proceso de compra de un automóvil y, en su caso, verificar el valor de permuta de su vehículo;
  * con terceros no afiliados para proporcionarle productos y servicios selectos (incluyendo, pero sin limitación, seguros de automóviles, servicio eléctrico seguro y sin interrupciones para conductores de i-MiEV, etc.);
  * cuando usted nos de su consentimiento para hacerlo, incluyendo si le notificamos acerca de los Sitios con los cuales compartiremos la información que nos proporcione de una manera en particular y usted nos proporciona dicha información;
  * con proveedores, contratistas, consultores y otros proveedores de servicios que trabajan en nuestro nombre y que necesitan tener acceso a su información para llevar a cabo su trabajo para nosotros;
  * para (i) cumplir con las leyes o responder a solicitudes legítimas y procesos legales, (ii) para proteger nuestros derechos y propiedades, así como los de nuestros agentes, clientes y otros, incluyendo hacer cumplir nuestros acuerdos, políticas y Condiciones de Uso o (iii) en caso de emergencia, para proteger a MMNA y la seguridad de nuestros clientes, empleados o terceros; y
  * en relación a una fusión o durante las negociaciones para la misma, una venta de activos corporativos, una restructura, reorganización, financiamiento o adquisición de la totalidad o de una parte de nuestro negocio por parte de otra compañía;.

También podremos compartir información agregada o anónima que no le identifique directamente. 

### Sus Derechos de Privacidad en California

Bajo la Ley Shine the Light de California, § 1798.83 del Código Civil de California, los residentes de California tienen derecho a solicitar y obtener, una vez al año, información acerca de la divulgación de información personal a terceros por parte de MMNA para sus propios fines de marketing directo. Para solicitar una lista de las categorías de información que MMNA ha compartido, y los nombres y direcciones de los terceros respectivos, por favor envíe su solicitud a:

Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc.  
Customer Relations Department  
PO Box 6400  
Cypress, CA 90630 

### Actualización de su Información

En caso de que usted haya proporcionado información personal a MMNA, usted podrá revisar y actualizar dicha información, iniciando sesión en su cuenta en línea.

### Opción de Opt Out y Corrección de su Información

Usted podrá optar por no recibir correos electrónicos promocionales y mensajes SMS de MMNA en cualquier momento visitando http://www.mitsubishicars.com/preferences y cambiando sus preferencias de comunicación. Para renunciar a recibir mensajes SMS, también podrá enviar un mensaje con el texto MITSUSTOP desde el teléfono celular que usted haya registrado en MMNA. Además, usted podrá optar por no recibir correos electrónicos promocionales siguiendo las instrucciones en dichos correos electrónicos, pero sírvase notar que todavía le enviaremos correos electrónicos no promocionales, tales como mensajes de correo electrónico sobre su cuenta o nuestras relaciones comerciales en curso. Usted también podrá solicitar cambios en sus preferencias de contacto y su información personal escribiendo a:

Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc.  
Customer Relations Department  
PO Box 6400  
Cypress, CA 90630 

### Seguridad de la Información

Tomamos medidas razonables para proteger la información personal en un esfuerzo para evitar su pérdida, mal uso y acceso no autorizado, divulgación, alteración y destrucción.

### Enlaces de Terceros

Nuestros Sitios pueden contener enlaces a sitios web de terceros. Esta política de privacidad no se aplica a los sitios vinculados, y no controlamos ni somos responsables por el contenido o prácticas de privacidad y de seguridad de estos sitios. Cualquier información personal que usted proporcione a un sitio vinculado será proporcionada directamente a un tercero y estará sujeta a la política de privacidad de dicho tercero. Le sugerimos conocer más sobre las prácticas y políticas de privacidad y seguridad de dicho tercero antes de proporcionar cualquier información personal.

### Contáctenos

Si usted tiene alguna pregunta o inquietud acerca de esta política de privacidad, por favor póngase en contacto con MMNA llamando al 1-888-MITSU (1-888-648-7820).

### Fecha de Vigencia de la Política de Privacidad

MMNA podrá modificar esta política de privacidad de vez en cuando. En caso de que MMNA haga alguna modificación a esta política, modificaremos la fecha de la "Última Actualización" que figura más abajo.

Última Actualización: 15 de octubre de 2013

### Política de Registros Electrónicos

Última Actualización: 16 de octubre de 2013

**Por favor, lea detenidamente este Política de Registros Electrónicos. Esta política le informa acerca de sus derechos cuando le proporcionemos ciertas revelaciones, avisos y otras informaciones ("Registros") por vía electrónica a través del sitio web mitsubishicars.com y por correo electrónico.**

Las palabras, "yo", "usted" y "su" se refieren al usuario que solicita información de este sitio web. Las palabras, "MMCA", "nosotros", "nuestro" y "nuestros" se refieren a Mitsubishi Motors Credit of America, Inc. y sus agentes y afiliados, incluyendo a Mitsubishi Motors North America, Inc. 

**(1) Introducción**  
Ciertas leyes nos obligan a proporcionarle determinados Registros específicos por escrito, lo que significa que usted tiene el derecho de recibir esos Registros en papel. Podemos proporcionarle dichos Registros electrónicamente si previamente le presentamos este Política de Registros Electrónicos y usted consiente la utilización de Registros electrónicos. Al indicar su aceptación de esta Política de Registros Electrónicos, usted acepta que su firma electrónica en acuerdos y documentos tenga el mismo efecto que si usted los hubiera firmado con tinta.

**(2) Tipos de Registros Electrónicos que Usted Podría Recibir**  
Al aceptar el uso de Registros electrónicos, usted reconoce el recibo de esta Política de Registros Electrónicos y usted da su consentimiento para recibir Registros electrónicamente. Los Registros podrán ser presentados en el sitio web mitsubishicars.com y por correo electrónico a la dirección de correo electrónico que usted proporcione (suponiendo que usted proporcione una dirección válida de correo electrónico). Los Registros electrónicos podrán incluir, pero sin limitarse a ellos:

  * Esta Política de Registros Electrónicos, y
  * El consentimiento para ser contactado por teléfono, y
  * Una oferta de crédito, en caso de ser elegible para la misma.

**(3) Cómo Retirar su Consentimiento**  
Su consentimiento para el uso de Registros electrónicos se mantendrá vigente hasta que sea retirado de la manera prevista en esta sección. Si usted retira su consentimiento, dejaremos de proporcionarle Registros electrónicos. Su retiro del consentimiento se aplicará sólo a la solicitud de servicios que usted está solicitando en este momento. Usted podrá retirar su consentimiento de forma gratuita enviándonos un correo electrónico a info@yourmitsu.com. Asegúrese de especificar su nombre y la dirección a la que deberemos enviar los Registros en el futuro según sea necesario. El retiro de su consentimiento tendrá vigencia sólo después de que MMCA haya tenido un plazo razonable para actuar sobre su solicitud de retiro.

**(4) Actualización de su Información de Contacto**  
En caso de que cambie su dirección de correo electrónico u otra información de contacto, deberá notificar de inmediato a MMCA acerca de dicho cambio enviándonos un correo electrónico a info@yourmitsu.com.

**(5) Obtención de Copias en Papel de Registros Electrónicos**  
Usted podrá imprimir o hacer una copia de los Registros electrónicos utilizando el botón "Imprimir" o utilizando la función de impresión de su computadora personal. A petición, le proporcionaremos una copia en papel de cualquier Registro. Deberemos recibir su solicitud dentro de los 60 días después de la fecha en la que pusimos el Registro electrónico a su disposición por primera vez. Usted podrá solicitar una copia en papel de cualquier Registro enviándonos un correo electrónico a info@yourmitsu.com. Asegúrese de especificar su nombre, el Registro específico del cual usted está solicitando una copia en papel y la dirección postal a la que deberemos enviárselo. No le cobraremos por una copia en papel del Registro.

**(6) Requisitos de Hardware y Software**  
Aunque usted podrá acceder y conservar los Registros electrónicos utilizando otro hardware y software, su computadora personal deberá contar con lo siguiente:

Un sistema operativo, tal como:

  * Windows NT, 2000, ME, XP, Vista, o Windows 7; o
  * Macintosh OS 10.x

Acceso a Internet y un navegador de Internet que soporte el estándar HTML y JavaScript, tal como el navegador que está utilizando para ver esta Política de Registros Electrónicos, o bien:

  * Microsoft Internet Explorer 8.0 o superior
  * Firefox 17.0 o superior
  * Safari 5.0 o superior

Proporcionaremos Registros electrónicos en el sitio web mitsubishicars.com y por correo electrónico, ya sea en formato HTML y/o en formato PDF. Para los Registros electrónicos proporcionados en formato PDF, se necesita Adobe Reader®. Usted podrá descargar una copia gratuita de Adobe Reader desde el sitio Web de Adobe en [ www.adobe.com.](http://www.adobe.com/) El enlace abrirá una nueva ventana. Usted es responsable de proporcionarnos una dirección de correo electrónico válida.

Para imprimir o descargar los Registros electrónicos deberá tener una impresora conectada a su computadora o hasta aproximadamente 1 MB de espacio de disco duro disponible para almacenar Registros electrónicos.

**(7) Conservación de Copias para sus Archivos**  
Le recomendamos imprimir o descargar una copia de esta Política de Registros Electrónicos y todos los demás Registros electrónicos para conservarlos en sus archivos personales. 

1 Manufacturer's Suggested Retail Price. Excludes destination/handling, tax, title, license etc. Retailer price, terms and vehicle availability may vary. See your Mitsubishi retailer for details.

2 Legal Disclaimer for I-MiEV:  
Manufacturer's Suggested Retail Price. Excludes destination/handling, tax, title, license etc. Retailer price, terms and vehicle availability may vary. Includes CHAdeMO DC quick-charge port, battery warming system and heated side-view mirrors. Destination/handling charges for Mitsubishi i-MiEV $850 ($975 Alaska/Hawaii). Actual prices set by retailer. Federal and state tax credits and/or rebates may be available "post- sale" (after purchase of the vehicle has been completed by the dealer). Consult your tax professional for details.
